Register to The Quincy Porter Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Correspondence, Series I
  - Congratulatory Letters - Pulitzer Prize, I.B
    - Hutchins, Margaret (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Jackson, Rose (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Kaufman, Louis and Annette (Box 3, Folder 39)
      1954 May 20 -- autograph letter signed
    - Kubie, Lawrence S. (Box 3, Folder 39)
      1954 May 8 -- typed letter signed
    - Laudenslager, Harold (Box 3, Folder 39)
      1954 May 10 -- typed letter signed
    - Lewis, Ward (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Lob, Nancy (Wilson) (Box 3, Folder 39)
      1954 May 12 -- autograph letter signed
    - Lockwood, Normand (Box 3, Folder 39)
      [1954 May] -- autograph letter signed
    - Loomis, Hubert H. (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - The Louisville Orchestra (Mary Helen Byck, president) (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - The Louisville Orchestra (Robert Whitney, director) (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - MacKinnon, Bob (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - McMullan, Frank (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Meyers, Emerson (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Monks, Ann (Box 3, Folder 40)
      1954 May 5 -- card
    - Moore, Earl V. (Box 3, Folder 40)
      1954 May 4 -- typed letter signed (copy)
    - Malhauser, Fred and Margaret (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Murdock, Kenneth B. (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Nathan, Robert (Box 3, Folder 40)
      [1954 May] -- typed letter signed
    - Oates, Whitney J. (Box 3, Folder 40)
      1954 May 7 -- typed letter signed
    - Osborn, Marie-Louise (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Osgood, Edward H., Jr. (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Parisot, Aldo and Ellen (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Peirce, John (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Porter, Lucius C. [cousin] (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Porter, Lyman [brother] (Box 3, Folder 40)
      1954 May 4 -- card
    - Porter, Lyman [brother] (Box 3, Folder 40)
      1954 May 3 -- telegram
    - Quimby, Arthur W. (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Roberts, Arthur (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Rogers, Alden (Box 3, Folder 41)
      1954 May 23 -- typed letter signed
    - Ross, Gilbert (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Schorer, Mark and Ruth (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Schrade, Els and Leo (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Semler, Grace (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Seymour, Charles (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Simonson, Mrs. Albert (Box 3, Folder 41)
      1954 May 13 -- typed letter signed
    - Sims, Ezra (Box 3, Folder 41)
      [1954 May] -- card
    - Slade, John A. (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Smith, Cora Welch (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Starbuck, Kathryn H. (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Strauss, John and Charlotte (Box 3, Folder 41)
      1954 May 16 -- autograph letter signed
    - Taplin, Frank E. (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Van Kleeck, Baltus B. (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Van Kleeck, Etheline (Box 3, Folder 41)
      1954 May 6 -- telegram
    - Webster, Beveridge (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Weld, Ellen Rubinstein (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Louise H ? (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Emmy ? (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Donald ? (Box 3, Folder 41)
      1954 May 11 -- typed letter signed
    - George ? (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Notification of award (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Notification of award (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Cards designed and printed by Porter (Box 3, Folder 41)
      1954 May 17 -- 2 printed thank-you cards
  - Correspondence Concerning Publication, Recording, etc., I.C
    (To and From Porter)
    - Affiliated Music Corp. (Box 3, Folder 42)
      1937 Oct 8 -- typed letter signed
    - Arrow Music Press, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 42)
      1938-1956 -- 4 typed letters signed
      1938-1956 -- 2 typed letters (copies) from Quincy Porter to above
      1 catalogue
      1955 Dec 31 -- 1 royalty statement
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
    - Associated Music Publishers, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 43)
      1949-1960 -- 24 typed letters signed
      1949-1960 -- 8 typed letters (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      1955-1964 -- 4 royalty statements
      1956 -- 3 check stubs
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
    - C.C. Birchard & Co. (Box 3, Folder 44)
      1939 Sep 20 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
    - Boosey & Hawkes, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 44)
      1962 Sep 28 -- typed letter signed
    - Broadcast Music, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 44)
      1950-1966 -- 11 typed letters signed
      1965 Apr 14 -- telegram (copy)
      1959-1965 -- 4 typed letters (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
    - Alexander Broude (Box 3, Folder 44)
      1956-1957 -- 4 typed letters signed
    - Composers Recordings, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 45-46)
      1958 Feb 6 -- card
      1964-1966 -- 4 typed letters signed from Quincy Porter to above
      1956-1959 -- 10 (carbon) memos, minutes of meetings
      1965-1966 -- 8 (photocopy) memos, minutes of meetings
      2 publicity material
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
    - Eble Music Company (Box 4, Folder 47)
      1960 Feb 24 -- card
      1960 Mar 1 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
    - Elkan, Henri (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Carl Fischer, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 47)
      1966 Feb 1 -- typed letter signed
      1944-1964 -- 2 royalty statements
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
    - Galaxy Music Corp. (Box 4, Folder 47)
      1964 Apr 15 -- typed letter signed (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
    - Gamble Hinged Music Co. (Box 4, Folder 47)
      1946-1950 -- 3 typed letters signed
      1947 Jan 15 -- typed letter signed (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
    - H.W. Gray Co., Inc. (Box 4, Folder 47)
      1958-1966 -- 8 typed letters signed
      1964 Feb 7 -- typed letter signed (copy)
      1964 Feb 5 -- typed letter signed from Quincy Porter to above
      1966 Mar 11 -- typed letter signed (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      1962 Feb 24 -- typed letter from Quincy Porter to above
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
    - Harcourt, Brace and Company, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 47)
      1950 Sep 15 -- typed letter signed
    - Leeds Music Corp. (Box 4, Folder 47)
      1944 Aug 8 -- typed letter signed
      1944 Aug 22 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
    - Loomis & Company (Hubert H. Loomis) (Box 4, Folder 48-49)
      1951-1966 -- 3 autograph letters signed
      1964 Apr 8 -- autograph letter signed (carbon)
      1949-1964 -- 14 typed letters signed
      1961 Apr 29 -- card
      1964 -- 2 typed letters signed from Quincy Porter to above
      1960 Dec 5 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      1964 -- 2 typed letters from Loomis & Co. to NOTES Magazine
      1943-1952 -- 31 (copies) invoice reports
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - Loomis & Company (Hubert H. Loomis) (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Melo-Tone Recording Studio (Box 4, Folder 50)
      1948 Jun 3 -- typed letter signed
    - Mercury Music Corp. (Box 4, Folder 50)
      1941-1952 -- 4 typed letters signed
      1964 Mar 13 -- typed letter signed (carbon)
      1964 Mar 12 -- typed letter signed from Quincy Porter to above
      1950 Feb 28 -- 1 royalty statement
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
    - Modern Music (Box 4, Folder 50)
      1942 Apr 7 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
    - Edwin H. Morris & Co., Inc. (Box 4, Folder 50)
      1953 Mar 2 -- typed letter signed
    - Music Press, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 51)
      1940-1947 -- 25 typed letters signed
      1942 Jul 25 -- typed letter signed from Quincy Porter to above
      1945 Mar 1 -- 1 royalty statement
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
    - Music Publishers' Association (Box 4, Folder 51)
      1965 Apr 12 -- typed letter signed
    - Music Publishers Holding Corporation (Box 4, Folder 51)
      1946-1950 -- 2 typed letters signed
    - Musical America (Box 4, Folder 52)
      1930 May 7 -- typed letter signed
    - The Musical Quarterly (Box 4, Folder 52)
      1948 -- 2 typed letters signed
    - New Music Edition (Box 4, Folder 52)
      1951 Jul 30 -- typed letter signed
    - Overtone Records (Box 4, Folder 52)
      1965 Nov 12 -- typed letter signed
      2 catalogues
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
    - C.F. Peters Corp. (Box 4, Folder 53-54)
      1958-1963 -- 4 autograph letters signed
      1960-1966 -- 20 typed letters signed
      1963 Jul 17 -- typed letter (carbon) to New York Philharmonic
      1961-1966 -- 16 typed letters (carbon) from Quincy Porter to C.F. Peters
      1963 Nov 1 -- typed letter (carbon) from Morris Tyler to C.F. Peters
      1963 Oct 4 -- typed letter (copy) from Philharmonic Orchestra Association to C.F. Peters
      1963 -- 1 performance report
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
    - Theodore Presser Company (Box 4, Folder 55)
      1956-1965 -- 5 typed letters signed
      1962-1965 -- 5 typed letters (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      1963 Jun 6 -- typed letter (copy) from Theodore Presser Co. to Morris Tyler
      1963 May 28 -- typed letter (copy) from Theodore Presser Co. to Charles J. Parker
      1963 Apr 8 -- typed letter (carbon) from Morris Tyler to Theodore Presser Co.
      1963 May 21 -- typed letter (carbon) from Charles Parker to Theodore Presser Co.
      1963 May 29 -- typed letter signed from Charles Parker to Quincy Porter
      1963 Jun 3 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to Charles Parker
      1963 Aug 1 -- typed letter signed from Morris Tyler to Quincy Porter
      1 royalty statement
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
    - Remick Music Corp. (Box 4, Folder 56)
      1961 Dec 2 -- 1 royalty statement
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
    - G. Schirmer, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 56)
      1950 Mar 3 -- typed letter signed
    - Valley Music Press (Box 4, Folder 56)
      1957 -- 3 autograph letters signed
      1946-1963 -- 9 typed letters signed
      1959-1962 -- 4 typed letters (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      1968 Apr 30 -- typed letter signed from Carl Berger to above
      1958 Jun 15 -- 1 royalty statement
      1956-1963 -- 7 catalogues
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
      - [unittitle added: see error report]
  - Correspondence with Performing Organizations, Radio Stations, Music Festivals, etc., I.D
    - American Wind Symphony (Box 5, Folder 57)
      1958-1959 -- 2 typed letters (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Bamberger Broadcasting Service, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 57)
      1935 Feb 28 -- autograph letter signed
      1935 -- 2 telegrams (scrapbook)
      See also: WOR Radio
    - British Broadcasting Company (Box 5, Folder 57)
      1958-1959 -- 9 typed letters signed
      1958-1959 -- 4 typed letters (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Budapest String Quartet (Box 5, Folder 57)
      1944 Sep 20 -- autograph letter signed
    - Cherry String Quartet (Box 5, Folder 57)
      1949 Oct 11 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
    - Cincinnati Symphony Orchestra (Box 5, Folder 57)
      1950 -- 5 typed letters signed
      1950-1952 -- 3 typed letters signed (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      [1950] -- 1 account of Quincy Porter letter to above
      1950 Dec 22 -- autograph letter signed (copy) from Thor Johnson to Morris Tyler
      1950 Dec 28 -- typed letter signed (copy) from Morris Tyler to Thor Johnson
    - Claremont Quartet (Box 5, Folder 58)
      1963 Jan 24 -- autograph letter signed
    - Columbia Artists Management, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 58)
      1949 -- 3 typed letters signed
    - Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 58)
      1938-1942 -- 6 typed letters signed (3-scrapbook)
    - Letters to CBS, from individuals, in response to Porter's Two Dances for Radio, broadcast during the "Everybody's Music Hour", August, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 59)
      - Archer, Douglas
        1938 Aug 14 -- card
      - Basham, Parma C.
        1938 Aug 15 -- card
      - Borbridge, Allen
        1938 Aug 18 -- autograph letter signed
      - Cerna, Lucas
        1938 Aug 16 -- typed letter signed
      - Converse, Luna B.
        1938 Aug 14 -- typed letter signed
      - Dabby, J.S.
      - Duffy, John J.
        [1938 Aug] -- 2 typed letters
      - Ferd, Olga Carolyn
        1938 Aug ? -- 2 autograph letters signed
      - Fry, Mary W.
      - Gossard, J.E., Jr.
        1938 Aug 14 -- autograph letter signed
      - Groff, Alden
        1938 Aug 16 -- card
      - Hoss, Wendell
        1938 Aug 18 -- card
      - Hudson, Betty
        1938 Aug 15 -- typed letter signed
      - Inslee, Edith N.
        1938 Aug 17 -- typed letter
      - Knox, A.J.
      - Levee, Naomi
        1938 Aug 15 -- autograph letter
      - Little, John S.
      - Lowenthal, Ben
      - McClean, Clara
      - Pilhashy, B.M.
      - Ruzicka, Edna May
      - Stevens, Charles D.
      - Sycamore ?
      - Thomas, Letta
        1938 Aug 22 -- typed letter signed
      - Wenzel, K.H.
    - Durieux Chamber Music Ensemble (Box 5, Folder 60)
      1937 -- 2 autograph letters signed (1-scrapbook)
      1938; No date -- 2 typed letters signed (1-scrapbook)
    - Fine Arts Quartet (Box 5, Folder 60)
      1959 Jun 23 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      See also: Dallas Chamber Music Society, Inc.
    - Instituto de Cultura Hispanica. I Festival de Música de América y España (Box 5, Folder 60)
      1964 -- 3 typed letters signed
      1964 -- 3 typed letters (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      1964 Oct -- 1 brochure
    - Lima Symphony Orchestra (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 60)
      1962 Oct 15 -- typed letter signed
    - Louisville Orchestra (Box 5, Folder 61)
      1962-1964 -- 4 typed letters signed
      1954 May 24 -- telegram
      1963 Nov 26 -- typed letter signed from Quincy Porter to above
      1964 Apr 27 -- typed letter signed (carbon)
      1962-1964 -- 2 typed letters (carbon)
      1 rough copy of speech delivered in Louisville
    - National Broadcasting Company, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 61)
      1937 Jul 8 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
      No year May 6 -- telegram (scrapbook)
    - National Symphony Orchestra (Box 5, Folder 61)
      1937; 1964 -- 2 typed letters signed (1-scrapbook)
      1964 Feb 14 -- typed letter signed from Quincy Porter to above
    - New Art Wind Quintet (Box 5, Folder 61)
      1949 Nov 5 -- typed letter signed
    - New Hampshire Music Festival, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 61)
      1961 Feb 8 -- typed letter signed
      1961 Mar 2 -- typed letter from Quincy Porter to above
      See also: general correspondence with Thomas Nee
    - New Haven Chorale, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 61)
      1965 Mar 17 -- typed letter signed
      1965 Mar 29 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - New Haven Symphony Orchestra (Box 5, Folder 61)
      1958-1960 -- 3 typed letters signed
      1958 Dec 8 -- typed letter signed (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - New York Philharmonic Symphony Society (Box 5, Folder 61)
      1937 -- 3 typed letters signed (scrapbook)
      1937 Mar 17 -- telegram (scrapbook)
    - New York String Sextet (Box 5, Folder 61)
      [1962-1963] -- 1 brochure
    - Philadelphia Orchestra Association (Box 5, Folder 62)
      1936-1937 -- 2 typed letters signed (scrapbook)
    - Roth String Quartet (Box 5, Folder 62)
      1937 Jul 2 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
    - Salzburg String Quartet (Box 5, Folder 62)
      1965 Jan 8 -- autograph letter signed
      1965 Jan 29 -- typed letter signed
    - Seattle Symphony Orchestra, Inc. (Box 5, Folder 62)
      1963-1964 -- 6 typed letters signed
      [1963] -- autograph letter signed (rough) from Quincy Porter to above
      1963-1964 -- 3 typed letters signed (carbon)
      1964 Nov 5 -- typed letter (carbon)
      See also: American Symphony League
    - Silvermine Guild Chamber Music Center (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Walden String Quartet (Box 5, Folder 62)
      1944-1945 -- 3 typed letters signed
    - Colonial Williamsburg (Box 5, Folder 62)
      1958 Mar 21 -- typed letter signed
    - WABC (Box 5, Folder 62)
      No year Oct 14 -- telegram (scrapbook)
    - WGAR (Box 5, Folder 62)
      1935 May 29 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
      No year Dec 30 -- telegram (scrapbook)
    - WNYC (Box 5, Folder 62)
      1945 Feb 15 -- typed letter signed
      1954 May 25 -- telegram draft from Quincy Porter to above
    - WOR. Music Library (Box 5, Folder 62)
      1939 Mar 6 -- typed letter (copy) from Quincy Porter to above
    - WQXR (Box 5, Folder 62)
      1939 Apr 8 -- typed letter signed
    - WUOM (Box 5, Folder 62)
      1950 Jul 10 -- typed letter signed
    - Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 63)
      1965 Dec 11 -- typed letter (carbon) from Fogel, Henry to Hi Fidelity Magazine
      1960 May 18 -- typed letter (copy) from Thorne, Oakleigh to Vegh String Quartet
  - Correspondence with Schools, Universities, etc., I.E
    - American Academy in Rome (Box 6, Folder 64)
      1921; 1960 -- 2 typed letters signed (1-scrapbook)
      1960 Oct 14 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - American Conservatory of Music (Box 6, Folder 64)
      1951 Mar 12 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
    - Antioch College (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Bard College (Box 6, Folder 64)
      1946 Dec 24 -- typed letter
    - Bennington College (Box 6, Folder 64)
      1950 Mar 18 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
    - Berkshire Music School - Tanglewood (Box 6, Folder 64)
      1964 Mar 12 -- typed letter signed (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      1960 -- 2 typed letters (carbon)
    - Black Mountain College (Box 6, Folder 64)
      1949 Nov 12 -- typed letter signed
    - Boston Music School, Inc. (Box 6, Folder 64)
      1945 Mar 30 -- typed letter signed (scrapbook)
    - Boston University. School of Fine & Applied Arts (Box 6, Folder 64)
      1964 Mar 27 -- typed letter signed
      1964 Apr 3 -- typed letter signed (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      1965 Jul 12 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Brandeis University (Box 6, Folder 64)
      1959 Mar 13 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Brooklyn College (Box 6, Folder 64)
      1960 Jun 2 -- typed letter signed
      1960 Jun 9 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Buffalo, University of (Box 6, Folder 64)
      1960 -- 2 typed letters signed
      1960 Oct 25 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - California. University at Berkeley (Box 6, Folder 65)
      1937; 1959 -- 3 typed letters signed (1-scrapbook)
      1959-1961; No date -- 3 typed letters (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - California. University of Southern California at Los Angeles (Box 6, Folder 65)
      1949 Dec 19 -- telegram (scrapbook)
    - California. State College, San Fernando Valley (Box 6, Folder 65)
      1958 Oct 15 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to Quincy Porter to above
    - Carnegie Institute of Technology (Box 6, Folder 65)
      1960 -- typed letters signed
      1960 Jan 11 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
      See also: general correspondence with Nikolai Lopatnikoff
    - The Chapin School (Box 6, Folder 65)
      1963-1964 -- 4 autograph letters signed
      1963-1964 -- 3 typed letters signed
    - Cleveland Institute of Music (Box 6, Folder 65)
      1931 Mar 11 -- typed letter signed
      1931 Mar 11 -- typed letter (carbon) from Maurice Hewitt to above
    - Columbia University. Teachers College (Box 6, Folder 65)
      1963 Nov 27 -- typed letter signed
      1963 Dec 4 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to Quincy Porter to above
    - Eastman School of Music
      See: University of Rochester
    - Florida. State College for Women at Tallahassee (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Fontainebleau Schools (Box 6, Folder 65)
      1964 Apr 20 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Grinnell College (Box 6, Folder 65)
      1958 Mar 18 -- typed letter signed
    - Julius Hartt School of Music (Box 6, Folder 66)
      1951 Aug 23 -- typed letter signed
    - Harvard University. Law School (Box 6, Folder 66)
      1965 Oct 29 -- typed letter signed
    - Harvard University. Music Department (Box 6, Folder 66)
      1950 Feb 24 -- typed letter signed (carbon)
    - Hill School. Alumni Association (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Howard College (Box 6, Folder 66)
      1953 Jun 22 -- typed letter signed
    - Idaho. University at Moscow (Box 6, Folder 66)
      1956 Jul 25 -- typed letter signed
    - Juilliard School of Music (Box 6, Folder 66)
      1947-1966 -- 3 typed letters signed (1-scrapbook)
    - Kansas. State College at Emporia (Box 6, Folder 66)
      1950; 1962 -- 2 typed letters signed (1-scrapbook)
      1962 Sep 5 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Kentucky. Western Kentucky State College at Bowling Green (Box 6, Folder 66)
      1964 Mar 3 -- typed letter signed
    - MacDowell Colony (Box 6, Folder 66)
      1961 Apr 19 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Massachusetts. University at Amherst (Box 6, Folder 66)
      1944; 1964 -- 2 typed letters signed (1-scrapbook)
      1964 Mar 11 -- typed letter signed (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology. Music Department (Box 6, Folder 66)
      1965 Jan 14 -- typed letter signed
      1965 Jan 29 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Michigan. University at Ann Arbor (Box 6, Folder 66)
      1946; 1954 -- 2 typed letters signed (1-scrapbook)
    - Middlebury College (Box 6, Folder 66)
      1963 Feb 21 -- typed letter (carbon) from Quincy Porter to above
    - Milton Academy (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Minnesota. University at Minneapolis (Box 6, Folder 66)
      1959 Mar 2 -- typed letter signed
    - Neighborhood Music School, Inc. (Box 6, Folder 67)
      1961 Aug 18 -- typed letter signed
    - New England Conservatory of Music (Box 6, Folder 67)
      1940-1965 -- 4 typed letters signed (1-scrapbook)
      1938 -- 2 telegrams (scrapbook)
      See also: Philip R. Allen; Wallace Goodrich
    - New England Conservatory of Music. Alumni Association (Box 6, Folder 67)
      1960 Mar 30 -- typed letter signed
    - New Hampshire. University at Durham (Box 6, Folder 67)